Division of Invertebrate Paleontology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Locality Information, Series II
  - Denmark. Locality information for Denmark including Greenland., 001308
    - Locality information. Locality information and faunal list of brachiopods, Cretaceous, Denmark., 1948; 000758
    - Locality information. Locality information, maps & lists: Greenland., 1965; 000313
    - Locality information. Locality information pertaining to accession 7084; Danish Greenland Expeditions, 000890
    - Locality information. Locality information - Northeast Greenland, 000891
  - England., 001278
    - Catalog of identifications. Catalog of fossil identifications: England. 1899, 1900, 000156
    - Locality information. Locality Information; Wales, 1948; 000662
    - Locality information. Locality information, British Isles (England, Ireland), Carboniferous., 1954; 000525
    - Locality information. Locality information; England., 1955; 000429
    - Locality information. Locality information; England, North Carolina, & Virginia., 1997; 000667
    - Locality information. Catalog of localities: Ordovician, Shropshire, England; P.T.O. means please turn over (they are not someone's initials)., 000163
  - Germany., 001309
    - Locality information. locality info.; Paffrath, Germany., 1904; 000374
    - Locality information. Hunsruck Slate, Bundenbach, Germany; additional specimen documentation including observations by FHCH; X-Ray of 224000, 000908
    - Locality information. Locality and strat. information for Devonian ophiuroids from Velbert, Germany, 000920
  - India., 001279
    - Locality information. locality information: Yale North India Expedition., 1932; 000462
    - Locality information. Locality information for the fossil material collected on the Indian Ocean islands visited during the Yale Seychelles Expedition., 1957; 000729
  - Ireland., 001310
    - Locality information. Ireland, Carboniferous, Gallagher paper, 1997; 000835
  - Miscellaneous. Locality information without country information., 001319
    - Locality information. Locality and section., 1910; 000372
    - Locality information. locality list: Formosa., 1939; 000404
    - Locality information. Locality register for Bretsky (1970) including brachipopods, bivalves and gastropods; dissertation., 000630
    - Locality information. Loc. information; Amber returned to IP Division from Entomology, about 1995., 2000; 000746
    - Locality information. Locality information for accession YPM.11339, 000936
  - Pakistan., 001315
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of localities: Salt Range, Pakistan; MSS by Newell and Hutchins., 1932; 000193
  - Russia. Locality information for Russia, including armenia. IPAR.001306., 001306
    - Locality information. Locality Information; Russia, 1984; 000663
    - Locality information. Locality information, Neogene of Armenia., 2000; 000736
    - Locality information. description of Pennsylvanian fusulinids within lots 40, 230, and 247: Russia; locality map for Kunlun (or Kun-lun), China (if that = K'un-lun. date unknown, 000392
  - South America., 001316
    - Locality information. locality info.; biographical info.; Bahia, 1867; 000784
    - Locality information. locality info.; Peru., 1912; 000375
    - Locality information. Locality map for mesozoic collections: Chile., 1919; 000226
    - Locality information. locality info; Panama; Miocene Gatun Fm., 2002; 000761
    - Locality information. Locality information for Tertiary molluscs: Peru., 000314
    - Locality information. Locality information for Recent, Pleistocene, & Pliocene Bryozoa of Panama/Carabbean Sea area, 000899
  - Spain., 001313
    - Locality information. Location map of fossil localities: Spain., 1966; 000166
  - Sweden., 001307
    - Locality information. Locality Register: Gotland, Sweden., 1921; 000494
    - Locality information. Silurian brachiopods and brachiopod biofacies of Gotland, Sweden: an excursion guide + highway map of Gotland, Sweden 1:300000, 2005; 000801
  - Switzerland., 001311
    - Locality information. locality details - fieldtrip to Porrentury, Switzerland, 000924
  - USA., 001276
    - Catalog of identifications. "Catalog of the fossil Lamellibranchiata of the Upper Helderberg, Hamilton, Portage, and Chemung Groups of the State of New York"; descr. in Palaeontology of NY vol. 5, pt.1., 1884; 000894
    - Catalog of identifications. Catalog of fossil identifications: Minnesota, Wisconsin., 1918; 000209
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of localities: Illinois., 1910; 000200
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of localities and maps from Ph.D. Dissertation: Oklahoma., 1910; 000266
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of localities, Missouri., 1944; 000393
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of Pierre localities & faunas: South Dakota., 1951; 000348
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of localities: Nevada., 1953; 000247
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of localities: Texas., 1957; 000154
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of localities for fusulinid collections: Texas., 1957; 000275
    - Catalog of localities. Locality information, Cambrian units of Utah, Gaines and Dietl collecting, 2005, 000811
    - Locality information. Locality maps pertaining to site IPE.07773, Indian Creek, Crawfordsville, IN., 2014; 002477
    - Locality information. Original letter and sketch of section describing accession YPM.01089. Also includes descriptions of Cretaceous 3 (site IPA.06537) and Cretaceous 5 (site IPA.06538)., 15 Feb 1878; 003196
    - Locality information. Report on localities & geology of brachiospongid area: Kentucky., 1867; 000242
    - Locality information. Non-original sketch map and section showing localities at Como Bluff: Wyoming., 1879; 000337
    - Locality information. Original locality descriptions and cross sections, maps: Wyoming., 1882; 000338
    - Locality information. Publication by Sheridan, P.H., 1882, with descriptions and map: Wyoming., 000339
    - Locality information. specimen & locality catalog, & loc. info.; New York, Vermont; Chazy; Chazyan, 1899; 000492
    - Locality information. Locality information; Pennsylvania, 1902; 000654
    - Locality information. Locality information; Wellington Sh, Banner City (=Elmo), Kansas, 1903; 000739
    - Locality information. Catalog of localities: Oklahoma. 1905, 1906, 1907, 000233
    - Locality information. locality and specimen information: Texas; with U.S.G.S. localities, 1906; 000403
    - Locality information. Locality information: Missouri., 1907; 000384
    - Locality information. Florissant, Colorado localities; Oligocene, 1907; 000874
    - Locality information. List of localities for Pennsylvanian fossils from around Belleview, Idaho., 1910; 000367
    - Locality information. Locality information; Arizona, Colorado, Utah, Montana. 1913-1914, 000669
    - Locality information. locality information: Oklahoma., 1918; 000383
    - Locality information. locality information; Ohio. 1924-1930, 000394
    - Locality information. Catalog and map of localities: Maine., 1925; 000189
    - Locality information. Old locality cards with taxonomic information: Wyoming., 1925; 000304
    - Locality information. locality & strat. info. & well log and detailed notes in 15 blue exam books, Tonkawa Oil Field, Noble Co., Oklahoma., 1925; 000366
    - Locality information. locality information for mainly Pennsylvanian brachiopods and fusulinids: Nebraska, Kansas, Missouri, Iowa [Volume=incomplete set (6 vols, locs 1-600) with incomplete info] 1925 - 1929, 000421
    - Locality information. locality information with photographic plates; Pennsylvanian: Nebraska, Kansas, Missouri, Iowa 1925 - 1929, 000422
    - Locality information. locality information for mainly Pennsylvanian brachiopods and fusulinids: Nebraska, Kansas, Missouri, Iowa [Volume=complete set (8 vols, locs 1-800) with complete info. and Pabian's notes in original ink. RP cannot find loc nos higher than 800] 1925 - 1929, 000508
    - Locality information. Catalog of Pierre & Fox Hills localities & faunas, and parts of Russell Yale dissertation: South Dakota., 1926; 000347
    - Locality information. locality information: Texas, Cretaceous., 1926; 000460
    - Locality information. locality labels (original); Texas; Lower Cretaceous., 1926; 000461
    - Locality information. Locality & stratigraphic information, & black and white prints of fusulines from Pennsylvanian - Permian Bird Spring Formation of Nevada. Black and white prints, 1927; 000568
    - Locality information. Locality information, Kickapoo Ls: Texas., 1929; 000391
    - Locality information. Locality info. & faunal list of species; Indiana, 1933; 000665
    - Locality information. locality information, Wyoming. 1933-1937, 000701
    - Locality information. Locality information, Connecticut, Killam's Point, Branford, 1933; 000727
    - Locality information. Catalog of localities: Texas., 1934; 000232
    - Locality information. Location map of fossil localities: California., 1936; 000205
    - Locality information. Locality information; Vermont (Shoreham)., 1936; 000653
    - Locality information. Map, sections, & faunal lists of Bird Spring Fm, Spring Mt, Clark County, Nevada; and Locality conversions, 1937; 000365
    - Locality information. locality information & fusulinid MS; Colorado., 1938; 000430
    - Locality information. Exerpts copied from Princeton Univ. senior thesis on Pierre Sh and Fox Hills Fm (2 copies), S. and N. Dakota, 1940; 000405
    - Locality information. locality information, Tennessee, 1941; 000527
    - Locality information. Notebook register of field photographs: Idaho, Utah. 1946, 1947, 1948, 1949, 000310
    - Locality information. Locality Information; New York, 1948; 000664
    - Locality information. locality information, maps & specimen lists; Utah, Idaho., 1949; 000498
    - Locality information. locality list: Nevada., 1950; 000402
    - Locality information. Locality info., Tenessee; from personal diary (partial segment form 1951), from 8th grade to present (1997). J.R. did not use field notebooks (personnal comm. to C. MacC., Aug, 1997), 2004 obituary, 000655
    - Locality information. 3 typed copies of locality lists for dissertation on Upper Devonian Spirifer disjunctus: New York, Pennsylvania, Ohio., 1953; 000322
    - Locality information. Locality infomation for dissertation collection of Cambrian invertebrate fossils from Pennsylania and Virgina, 1953; 000445
    - Locality information. Locality information: Pennsylvania., 1953; 000495
    - Locality information. Measured sections for dissertation on Pennsylvanina & Permian fossils: Arizona. 1953, 1954, 000312
    - Locality information. locality information from thesis: Utah, 1954; 000439
    - Locality information. Catalog of localities: Missouri., 1955; 000168
    - Locality information. map of "Mazon Creek" localities, Illinois (from fig. 3 of reprint 6354; Richardson), 1956; 000887
    - Locality information. Strat. Sections and cc of geologic map from dissertation: Arizona, Whetstone Mt., 1957; 000376
    - Locality information. Texas, Permian, R.H. Cress locs, Fusulinacea, 1957; 000836
    - Locality information. Catalog of localities: Colorado, South Dakota, Wyoming., 1958; 000161
    - Locality information. Location map of fossil localities from dissertation; reprint of Anaktuvik Pass area; map from another reprint: Alasaka., 1960; 000188
    - Locality information. Key to samples from Long Island Sound: Long Island Sound., 1960; 000214
    - Locality information. Locality data in Woodring, W.P., et al, 1940, USGS Prof. Paper 195: California., 1960; 000297
    - Locality information. locality information from Bloom's published Yale dissertation: Maine, 1960; 000443
    - Locality information. Long Island Sound: Western Part (1: 80000). Buzas, M.A.: Coastal., 1960; 001596
    - Locality information. locality information: South Dakota, 1961; 000444
    - Locality information. locality information; Illinois., 1961; 000504
    - Locality information. Measured sections, locality list, Yale undergraduate thesis: South Dakota., 1962; 000302
    - Locality information. Locality information, Hueco Mountains, Texas-New Mexico dissertation, 1962; 000531
    - Locality information. locality information; Oligocene Antero Fm, Colorado; Insecta - & numbered specimens transferred from Paleobotany Division, 1962; 000862
    - Locality information. partial list of locality conversion nos. for 1963 publ.with Ross, C.A.: Arizona., 000397
    - Locality information. Locality information: Alaska., 1964; 000357
    - Locality information. locality information: Maine, Spider Lake., 1964; 000423
    - Locality information. locality information; in part of B.A.H. Yale 1964 dissertation on geology of Spider Lake Quad, Maine, 000759
    - Locality information. Location map of fossil localities: Connecticut., 1966; 000204
    - Locality information. Locality information (including 1972 MS); Montana, Cretaceous., 1966; 000435
    - Locality information. locality information: Minnesota., 1966; 000493
    - Locality information. Locality register from dissertation on biogenic structures: New York, Wyoming. 1970, 1971, 000324
    - Locality information. documents related to Holocene insects from Stiles Clay Pit, Hamden, coll. by Denise Gaudreau, 1976, 1977: maps, paper by Gaudreau, systematic list of specimens., 002425
    - Locality information. Catalog of localities: Alabama, Louisiana., 1978; 000170
    - Locality information. Locality information for Newark Supergroup project, includes map of Solite Quarry: North Carolina, Virginia., 1978; 000191
    - Locality information. Locality information for Coon Creek, Mississippi., 1978; 000529
    - Locality information. Notes on localities: New York., 1980; 000172
    - Locality information. Photocopied maps for collections, unpublished papers related to collections: Arizona, California. 1981, 1982, 1983, 000295
    - Locality information. Locality information; Late Triassic & Early Jurassic of Connecticut & Massachusetts. exerpts from Field trip guidebook; N.E.I.G.C. 74th Ann. Mtng. Oct 2 & 3, 1982. [Volume=N.5], 000688
    - Locality information. Field notebook, section, etc., for collection of Pierre Sh fossils: Wyoming., 1983; 000305
    - Locality information. Locality information: Wyoming., 1984; 000360
    - Locality information. locality information: North Carolina, Virginia, and Baja California, Mexico., 1985; 000442
    - Locality information. Locality information; Early Jurassic of Connecticut, Rhode Island & New York. exerpts from N.E.I.G.C., 77th ann Mtng., Field Guidebook; Oct. 4-6, 1985; article by LeTourneau & McDonald. [Volume=N.6], 000691
    - Locality information. Locality information: New York, Devonian., 1986; 000432
    - Locality information. Locality information; Late Triassic of North Carolina. exerpts from S.E.P.M. Field Guidebook, 3rd ann. mtng, 1986, Textoris, ed., Gore., 000693
    - Locality information. Locality information; Late Triassic of North Carolina. exerpts from article by Wheeler & Textoris, 1978., 1986; 000694
    - Locality information. Locality information; Early Jurassic of Virginia. exerpts from Masters Thesis by Hentz, T.F., 1981, U. of Kansas, 1986; 000695
    - Locality information. USGS locality documents for conodont collection:., 1989; 000273
    - Locality information. locality information: Montana and Wyoming; Cretaceous., 1992; 000387
    - Locality information. locality information; New Mexico, Ohio, North Carolina, Connecticut., 1992; 000538
    - Locality information. locality information; New York, Jaycox Creek; Pennsylvania, 1996; 000523
    - Locality information. locality information; Massachusetts; Jurassic., 1997; 000539
    - Locality information. Locality information; Connecticut, Jurassic., 1997; 000648
    - Locality information. Catalog of Olsen localities (Triassic & Jurassic of eastern North America) compiled by Huber; photocopy., 1997; 000668
    - Locality information. Locality information for Kinzers Fm & Antietam Ss, Pennsylvania (including Getz farm quarry) coppied from Franklin & Marshall Masters thesis by L.D Campbell., 1999; 000710
    - Locality information. locality information, correspondance (Glenister, Feldman), & "Explorer" article; Iowa, 2000; 000740
    - Locality information. Locality information, Eureka Co., Nevada, 2001; 000741
    - Locality information. Locality info., Prospect Beach, West Haven, Connecticut, Holocene., 2001; 000744
    - Locality information. locality & specimen information; Montana; Cretaceous, Pierre Sh., 2001; 000747
    - Locality information. locality information; Holocene, Post-glacial, Connecticut (West Haven), 2002; 000767
    - Locality information. locality information; Holocene, Post-glacial, Connecticut (West Haven), 2002; 000769
    - Locality information. locality information; photocopy of quad. map of Holyoke, Massachusetts., 2003; 000771
    - Locality information. locality information; Cambrian, Wisconsin, Scyphozoa., 2004; 000785
    - Locality information. Fusulinidae localities for Kansas, New Mexico, Oklahoma, Texas (T-153 eg), Utah; Wolfcampian, Permian; (taken from Thompson, 1954), 2004; 000787
    - Locality information. locality information for Cretaceous gastropods from Utah, 2004; 000788
    - Locality information. locality information, Gower Fm, Iowa, 2004; 000791
    - Locality information. locality info., Pennsylvanian, Nevada, 2004; 000793
    - Locality information. locality information, Pennsylvanian, Knob Noster, Missouri., 2004; 000794
    - Locality information. Locality information, excerpts from: "Field trip and seminar on the Fort Payne Formation", 2004; 000950
    - Locality information. locality information, Rochester Sh, New York., 2005; 000795
    - Locality information. locality information, Cambrian, Nevada, 2007; 000881
    - Locality information. Locality info., Devonian Mount Marion Fm, New York; guidebook, 2007; 000884
    - Locality information. Geology of the Glass Mountains, Texas. Part I & II, Geology & Paleontology (includes notes regarding localities by MacClintock, 09/22/88): Texas. In 3 packages., 000249
    - Locality information. Locality register in Illinois State Geological Survey Bulletin no. 67: Illinois., 000369
    - Locality information. locality information, Lance Creek, Wyoming, Cretaceous, 000807
    - Locality information. Locality info, Lower Cambrian, western Nevada, Poleta Fm., 000812
    - Locality information. Locality information for Sam Ciurca collections; mostly Silurian of New York, Eurypterida, some Silurian of Indiana & Ohio, 000823
    - Locality information. Ciurca Collection Localities Lists; mostly Silurian of New York, Eurypterida and GPS Coordinates, 000826
    - Locality information. Nevada, Permian, E. Thomas Thesis locs., Fusulinacea, 000830
    - Locality information. Arizona, New Mexico, Mississippian, Pennsylvanian, P.K. Spencer thesis locs,., Fusulinacea, 000831
    - Locality information. Washington, Mississippian, Permian, J.E. Liszak thesis locs., Fusulinacea, 000832
    - Locality information. Kansas, Nebraska, Misouri, Iowa, Pennsylvanian, R.O. Schrott thesis locs., Fusulinacea, 000833
    - Locality information. Chester R. Longwell field labels from Permian and Triassic of Arrow Canyon, 000850
    - Locality information. Locality Info., Montana, Ruby Paper Sh, & Beaverhead, Insecta, 000863
    - Locality information. Harding Ss of Canyon City, Colorado, 000879
    - Locality information. Locality information, Ordovician New York, Beecher's Bed equivalent strata, 000898
    - Locality information. locality information, New York Ordovician, 000901
    - Locality information. Locality information: Additional NY collection localities of Ciurca, 000904
    - Locality information. Mississippian ophiuroids and trace fossils (Asteriacites) from Alabama; additional specimen documentation including observations by FHCH, 000912
    - Locality information. Pennsylvanian, from Oklahoma, Kansas, and Missouri; additional specimen documentation including observations by FHCH, 000913
    - Locality information. Pennsylvania, Crawford County, Mississippian, Echinoidea, 000915
    - Locality information. Locality information & map for Holocene concretion, Prospect Beach, West Haven, Connecticut, 000963
    - Locality information. Camarocrinus (=Scyphocrinites) from Late Silurian/Early Devonian Madrid Fm, Birch Point, Mattawamkeag Lake, Aroostook County, Maine, 000964
    - Locality information. Locality information - Green River insects, 000983
    - Locality map. Locality information for material from accn YPM.12519, 002741
    - Locality sketch. Sketch and description of locality 1 (San Ysidro quadrangle, T15N, R1W), 002729
    - Stratigraphic section. Stratigraphic sections: New Mexico, Texas, Arizona., 1935; 000230
    - Stratigraphic section. Measured section; Cretaceous, Wind River Mtns, Wyoming, 1940; 000817
    - Stratigraphic section. Measured sections with collecting localities for Glass, Delaware & Guadalupe Mountains: Texas., 000250
    - Catalogs and correspondence detailing the taxonomy and localities of specimens received from Charles Sternberg. Sternberg numbers in large black type on white rectangular stickers affixed to specimens can be correlated (if the age is known) to a list here., 1924-1925; 002707
    - Devonian Stratigraphy and Paleontology of the Roberts Mountains Region, Nevada, 1940; 000926
    - Locality information for Bangor Ls specimens from YPM.12760, 2018; 003221
    - Locality map for ophiuroid specimens collected on a peninsula in Cedar Creek Reservoir, Franklin County, Alabama (IPF.03004)., 003022
  - IP Division Locality Card [Cards] Catalog, scanned by YPPS and attached here as Multimedia files., 002702
- Photographs, Series III
  - Localities., 001282
    - Photographs & Negatives. Contact prints & negatives: Idaho, Utah. 1946, 1947, 1948, 1949, 000311
    - Photographs & Negatives. Photos of Peabody Museum Room 5, Invertebrate Paleontology collections and work room, prior to disassembling the work room, 1998; 000856
    - Photographs. Locality photographs with descriptions, 1907; 000893
    - Photographs. Geologic cross section and photo plates (all with locality info.) of Treasure Mt. Dome area: Colorado., 1936; 000352
    - Photographs. photographs, map, and stratigraphic column of collection locality, D6773, D6774, D6775, 000805
  - People., 001283
    - Biographical Material. Photographs of Clifton Sarle, assembled by Sam Ciurca, 1908-1958; 003188
    - Biographical Material. Photographs of Sam Ciurca, mostly in the field., 1963-1975; 002718
    - Biographical Material. Miscellaneous photographs of Charles Schuchert, 000927
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints and 8x10 negative of GSA Fellows(1889-1899) Black and White prints; 8X10 negatives. 1889-1899, 000586
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of J.E. Harding; Mesozoic in Chile Black and white prints, 1922; 000580
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints and a negative, taken by W.K. Sacco on July 7, 1987, of Schuchert and Dunbar. black and white prints and negative, 1932; 000588
    - Photographs & Negatives. 4X5 black and white negative of Gorgio Panella black and white negative, 1965; 000590
    - Photographs & Negatives. Photographs donated to IP; including Ed Leith, CO Dunbar, C Schuchert, Yang, JB Knight, RS Lull, RM Logie, P Wilson, Moneymaker, Longwell, Knopf, Flint, GE Lewis, Bateman, GA Cooper, PE Morris, Art Miller, N Newell, Thorpe: @ 1931-1935., 2000; 000728
    - Photographs & Negatives. Paleontological Society - photographs (scanned photos and negatives printed on laser printer) for the 100 anniversary: historical photos, photo album from 100th anniversary dinner (at Houston, TX, GSA) and additional dinner photos, 2008; 000923